<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="movieinfoitemname">
        <item>Director</item>
        <item>Genre</item>
        <item>Overview</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviebladerunner2049">
        <item>Denis Villeneuve</item>
        <item>Action · Drama · Mystery · Sci-Fi · Thriller</item>
        <item>Blade Runner 2049 is a 2017 American epic neo-noir science fiction film directed by Denis Villeneuve and written by Hampton Fancher and Michael Green.
            A sequel to the 1982 film Blade Runner, the film stars Ryan Gosling and Harrison Ford, with Ana de Armas, Sylvia Hoeks, Robin Wright, Mackenzie Davis, Dave Bautista,
            and Jared Leto in supporting roles. Ford and Edward James Olmos reprise their roles from the original film. Gosling plays K, a Nexus-9 replicant "blade runner" who uncovers
            a secret that threatens to destabilize society and the course of civilization.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviestarwars8">
        <item>Rian Johnson</item>
        <item>Action · Adventure · Fantasy · Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Star Wars: The Last Jedi is a 2017 American epic space opera film written and directed by Rian Johnson. Produced by Lucasfilm and
            distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures, it is the second installment of the Star Wars sequel trilogy, following
            The Force Awakens, and the eighth episode of the nine-part "Skywalker saga". The film\'s ensemble cast includes Mark Hamill,
            Carrie Fisher, Adam Driver, Daisy Ridley, John Boyega, Oscar Isaac, Andy Serkis, Lupita Nyong\'o,
            Domhnall Gleeson, Anthony Daniels, Gwendoline Christie, Kelly Marie Tran, Laura Dern, and Benicio del Toro.
            The Last Jedi follows Rey as she seeks the aid of Luke Skywalker, in hopes of turning the tide for the Resistance in the
            fight against Kylo Ren and the First Order, while General Leia Organa, Finn, and Poe Dameron attempt to escape a First Order
            attack on the dwindling Resistance fleet. The film features the first posthumous film performance by Fisher, who died in December
            2016, and the film is dedicated to her memory.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movietheoryofeverything">
        <item>James Marsh</item>
        <item>Biography · Drama · Romance</item>
        <item>In the 1960s, Cambridge University student and future physicist Stephen Hawking (Eddie Redmayne) falls in love with fellow
            collegian Jane Wilde (Felicity Jones). At 21, Hawking learns that he has motor neuron disease. Despite this -- and with Jane
            at his side -- he begins an ambitious study of time, of which he has very little left, according to his doctor. He and Jane
            defy terrible odds and break new ground in the fields of medicine and science, achieving more than either could hope to imagine.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviecoco">
        <item>Lee Unkrich · Adrian Molina</item>
        <item>Animation · Adventure · Comedy · Family · Fantasy · Music · Mystery</item>
        <item>Despite his family\'s generations-old ban on music, young Miguel dreams of becoming an
            accomplished musician like his idol Ernesto de la Cruz. Desperate to prove his talent, Miguel
            finds himself in the stunning and colorful Land of the Dead. After meeting a charming trickster named
            Héctor, the two new friends embark on an extraordinary journey to unlock the real story behind Miguel\'s family history.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviehitmansbodyguard">
        <item>Patrick Hughes</item>
        <item>Action · Comedy · Crime · Thriller</item>
        <item>The world\'s top protection agent is called upon to guard the life of his mortal enemy,
            one of the world\'s most notorious hit men. The relentless bodyguard and manipulative assassin have
            been on the opposite end of the bullet for years and are thrown together for a wildly outrageous 24 hours.
            During their journey from England to the Hague, they encounter high-speed car chases, outlandish boat escapades
            and a merciless Eastern European dictator who is out for blood.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviekongskullisland">
        <item>Jordan Vogt-Roberts</item>
        <item>Action · Adventure · Fantasy · Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Scientists, soldiers and adventurers unite to explore a mythical, uncharted island in the Pacific Ocean.
            Cut off from everything they know, they venture into the domain of the mighty Kong, igniting the ultimate
            battle between man and nature. As their mission of discovery soon becomes one of survival, they must fight to escape
            from a primal world where humanity does not belong.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviedarktower">
        <item>Nikolaj Arcel</item>
        <item>Action · Adventure · Fantasy · Sci-Fi · Western</item>
        <item>Roland Deschain (Idris Elba), the last Gunslinger, is locked in an eternal battle with Walter
            O\'Dim (Matthew McConaughey), also known as the Man in Black. The Gunslinger must prevent the Man in
            Black from toppling the Dark Tower, the key that holds the universe together. With the fate of worlds at stake,
            two men collide in the ultimate battle between good and evil.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviebabydriver">
        <item>Edgar Wright</item>
        <item>Action · Crime · Drama · Music</item>
        <item>Talented getaway driver Baby (Ansel Elgort) relies on the beat of his personal soundtrack to be the best
            in the game. After meeting the woman (Lily James) of his dreams, he sees a chance to ditch his shady lifestyle
            and make a clean break. Coerced into working for a crime boss (Kevin Spacey), Baby must face the music as a doomed
            heist threatens his life, love and freedom.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviepost">
        <item>Steven Spielberg</item>
        <item>Biography · Drama · History · Thriller · War</item>
        <item>Katharine Graham is the first female publisher of a major American newspaper -- The Washington Post.
            With help from editor Ben Bradlee, Graham races to catch up with The New York Times to expose a massive cover-up
            of government secrets that spans three decades and four U.S. presidents. Together, they must overcome their differences
            as they risk their careers -- and very freedom -- to help bring long-buried truths to light.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviegoodtime">
        <item>Benny Safdie · Josh Safdie</item>
        <item>Crime · Drama · Thriller</item>
        <item>A bank robber stops at nothing to free his brother from prison, launching himself into
            a nightlong odyssey through New York\'s dark and dangerous criminal underworld.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movieshapeofwater">
        <item>Guillermo del Toro</item>
        <item>Drama · Fantasy · Romance</item>
        <item>Elisa is a mute, isolated woman who works as a cleaning lady in a hidden, high-security government
            laboratory in 1962 Baltimore. Her life changes forever when she discovers the lab\'s classified secret -- a mysterious,
            scaled creature from South America that lives in a water tank. As Elisa develops a unique bond with her new friend,
            she soon learns that its fate and very survival lies in the hands of a hostile government agent and a marine biologist.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviealiencovenant">
        <item>Ridley Scott</item>
        <item>Horror · Sci-Fi · Thriller</item>
        <item>Bound for a remote planet on the far side of the galaxy, members (Katherine Waterston, Billy Crudup) of the colony
            ship Covenant discover what they think to be an uncharted paradise. While there, they meet David (Michael Fassbender),
            the synthetic survivor of the doomed Prometheus expedition. The mysterious world soon turns dark and dangerous when a
            hostile alien life-form forces the crew into a deadly fight for survival.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviesplit">
        <item>M. Night Shyamalan</item>
        <item>Horror · Thriller</item>
        <item>Though Kevin (James McAvoy) has evidenced 23 personalities to his trusted psychiatrist, Dr. Fletcher (Betty Buckley),
            there remains one still submerged who is set to materialize and dominate all of the others. Compelled to abduct three
            teenage girls led by the willful, observant Casey, Kevin reaches a war for survival among all of those contained
            within him -- as well as everyone around him -- as the walls between his compartments shatter.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviesixthsense">
        <item>M. Night Shyamalan</item>
        <item>Drama · Mystery · Thriller</item>
        <item>Young Cole Sear (Haley Joel Osment) is haunted by a dark secret: he is visited by ghosts. Cole is frightened by
            visitations from those with unresolved problems who appear from the shadows. He is too afraid to tell anyone about
            his anguish, except child psychologist Dr. Malcolm Crowe (Bruce Willis). As Dr. Crowe tries to uncover the truth about
            Cole\'s supernatural abilities, the consequences for client and therapist are a jolt that awakens them both to something
            unexplainable.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movieeverythingeverywhereallatonce">
        <item>Daniel Kwan · Daniel Scheinert</item>
        <item>Action · Adventure · Comedy · Fantasy · Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Directed by Daniel Kwan and Daniel Scheinert, collectively known as Daniels, the film is a hilarious and
            big-hearted sci-fi action adventure about an exhausted Chinese American woman (Michelle Yeoh) who can\'t seem to
            finish her taxes.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movieamancalledotto">
        <item>Marc Forster</item>
        <item>Comedy · Drama</item>
        <item>Based on the comical and moving New York Times bestseller, A Man Called Otto tells the story of Otto Anderson
            (Tom Hanks), a grumpy widower whose only joy comes from criticizing and judging his exasperated neighbors. When a
            lively young family moves in next door, he meets his match in quick-witted and very pregnant Marisol, leading to
            an unexpected friendship that will turn his world upside-down.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>