<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="novelinfoitemname">
        <item>Year Publishing</item>
        <item>Genre</item>
        <item>Overview</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelkokoro">
        <item>1914</item>
        <item>Fiction · Cultural · Classics · Asian Literature · Literature · Novels · Literary Fiction</item>
        <item>Hailed by The New Yorker as "rich in understanding and insight,"
            Kokoro—"the heart of things"—is the work of one of Japan\'s most popular authors. This
            thought-provoking trilogy of stories explores the very essence of loneliness and stands as a stirring
            introduction to modern Japanese literature.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelwishyouhere">
        <item>2021</item>
        <item>Fiction · Contemporary · Romance · Adult · Adult Fiction · Womens Fiction · Realistic Fiction · Literary Fiction · Historical</item>
        <item>A deeply moving novel about the resilience of the human spirit in a moment of crisis. Diana O\'Toole is
            perfectly on track. She will be married by thirty, done having kids by thirty-five,
            and move out to the New York City suburbs, all while climbing the professional ladder in
            the cutthroat art auction world. She\'s not engaged just yet, but she knows her boyfriend, Finn,
            a surgical resident, is about to propose on their romantic getaway to the Galapagos—days before her thirtieth birthday.
            Right on time. But then a virus that felt worlds away has appeared in the city,
            and on the eve of their departure, Finn breaks the news: It\'s all hands on deck at the hospital.
            He has to stay behind. You should still go, he assures her, since it would be a shame for all of their nonrefundable
            trip to go to waste. And so, reluctantly, she goes. Almost
            immediately, Diana\'s dream vacation goes awry. The whole island is now under quarantine, and she is stranded
            until the borders reopen. Completely isolated, she must venture beyond her comfort zone. Slowly, she carves out a
            connection with a local family when a teenager with a secret opens up to Diana, despite her father\'s suspicion of outsiders.
            Diana finds herself examining her relationships, her choices, and herself—and wondering if when she goes\' home, she too will have evolved into someone completely different.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelourmissinghearts">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Fiction · Dystopia · Audiobook · Contemporary · Literary Fiction · Science Fiction · Adult · Adult Fiction · Mystery · Thriller</item>
        <item>A novel about a mother\'s unbreakable love in a world consumed by fear.
            Twelve-year-old Bird Gardner lives a quiet existence with his loving but broken father,
            a former linguist who now shelves books in a university library. Bird knows to not ask too many questions,
            stand out too much, or stray too far. For a decade, their lives have been governed by laws written to
            preserve "American culture" in the wake of years of economic instability and violence. To keep the peace and restore
            prosperity, the authorities are now allowed to relocate children of dissidents, especially those of Asian origin, and
            libraries have been forced to remove books seen as unpatriotic—including the work of Bird\'s mother, Margaret,
            a Chinese American poet who left the family when he was nine years old. Bird has grown up disavowing his mother and her poems;
            he doesn\'t know her work or what happened to her, and he knows he shouldn\'t wonder. But when he receives a mysterious letter
            containing only a cryptic drawing, he is pulled into a quest to find her. His journey will take him back to the many folktales
            she poured into his head as a child, through the ranks of an underground network of librarians, into the lives of the children who
            have been taken, and finally to New York City, where a new act of defiance may be the beginning of much-needed change.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelotherbirds">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Fiction · Magical Realism · Fantasy · Contemporary · Romance · Adult · Paranormal · Adult Fiction · Ghosts · Mystery</item>
        <item>An enchanting tale filled with magical realism and moments of pure love that won\'t let you go.
            Between the real and the imaginary, there are stories that take flight in the most extraordinary ways.
            Right off the coast of South Carolina, on Mallow Island, The Dellawisp sits—a stunning old cobblestone building shaped like a horseshoe, and named after the tiny turquoise birds who, alongside its human tenants, inhabit an air of magical secrecy.
            When Zoey comes to claim her deceased mother\'s apartment at the Dellawisp she meets her quirky and secretive neighbors, including a young woman with a past, two estranged middle-aged sisters, and a lonely chef, and three ghosts. The sudden death of one of Zoey\'s new neighbors sets off a search that leads to the island\'s famous author and to a long-estranged relative of the sisters.
            Each of them has a story, and each story has an ending which hasn\'t yet been written.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelmadhoney">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Fiction · Mystery · Contemporary · Audiobook · Romance · LGBT · Thriller · Adult · Mystery Thriller · Adult Fiction</item>
        <item>A soul-stirring novel about what we choose to keep from our past, and what we choose to leave behind.
            Olivia McAfee knows what it feels like to start over. Her picture-perfect life—living in Boston, married to a brilliant cardiothoracic surgeon, raising a beautiful son,
            Asher—was upended when her husband revealed a darker side. She never imagined she would end up back in her sleepy New Hampshire hometown, living in the house she grew up in, and taking over her father\'s beekeeping business.
            Lily Campanello is familiar with do-overs, too. When she and her mom relocate to Adams, New Hampshire, for her final year of high school, they both hope it will be a fresh start.
            And for just a short while, these new beginnings are exactly what Olivia and Lily need. Their paths cross when Asher falls for the new girl in school, and Lily can\'t help but fall for him, too. With Ash, she feels happy for the first time. Yet at times, she wonders if she can she trust him completely . . .
            Then one day, Olivia receives a phone call: Lily is dead, and Asher is being questioned by the police. Olivia is adamant that her son is innocent. But she would be lying if she didn\'t acknowledge the flashes of his father\'s temper in him, and as the case against him unfolds, she realizes he\'s hidden more than he\'s shared with her.
            Mad Honey is a riveting novel of suspense, an unforgettable love story, and a moving and powerful exploration of the secrets we keep and the risks we take in order to become ourselves.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelhonor">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Fiction · Historical Fiction · India · Contemporary · Audiobook · Literary Fiction · Adult · Asia · Cultural · Adult Fiction</item>
        <item>In this riveting and immersive novel, bestselling author Thrity Umrigar tells the story of two couples and the sometimes dangerous
            and heartbreaking challenges of love across a cultural divide.
            Indian American journalist Smita has returned to India to cover a story, but reluctantly: long ago she and her family left
            the country with no intention of ever coming back. As she follows the case of Meena—a Hindu woman attacked by members of her
            own village and her own family for marrying a Muslim man—Smita comes face to face with a society where tradition carries more
            weight than one\'s own heart, and a story that threatens to unearth the painful secrets of Smita\'s own past. While Meena\'s fate
            hangs in the balance, Smita tries in every way she can to right the scales. She also finds herself increasingly drawn to Mohan,
            an Indian man she meets while on assignment. But the dual love stories of Honor are as different as the cultures of Meena and
            Smita themselves: Smita realizes she has the freedom to enter into a casual affair, knowing she can decide later how much it
            means to her.
            In this tender and evocative novel about love, hope, familial devotion, betrayal, and sacrifice, Thrity Umrigar shows us two
            courageous women trying to navigate how to be true to their homelands and themselves at the same time.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelthistimetomorrow">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Fiction · Science Fiction · Contemporary · Fantasy · Adult · Adult Fiction · Magical Realism · Literary Fiction</item>
        <item>What if you could take a vacation to your past?
            With her celebrated humor, insight, and heart, beloved New York Times
            bestseller Emma Straub offers her own twist on traditional time travel tropes, and a different kind of love story.
            On the eve of her 40th birthday, Alice\'s life isn\'t terrible. She likes her job, even if it isn\'t exactly the one
            she expected. She\'s happy with her apartment, her romantic status, her independence, and she adores her lifelong best
            friend. But her father is ailing, and it feels to her as if something is missing. When she wakes up the next morning she
            finds herself back in 1996, reliving her 16th birthday. But it isn\'t just her adolescent body that shocks her, or seeing
            her high school crush, it\'s her dad: the vital, charming, 40-something version of her father with whom she is reunited.
            Now armed with a new perspective on her own life and his, some past events take on new meaning. Is there anything that she
            would change if she could?</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="novelnotesexecution">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Fiction · Thriller · Mystery · Mystery Thriller · Contemporary · Audiobook · Literary Fiction · Crime · Adult · Suspense</item>
        <item>In the tradition of Long Bright River and The Mars Room, a gripping and atmospheric work of literary suspense that deconstructs the story of a serial killer on death row, told primarily through the eyes of the women in his life—from the bestselling author of Girl in Snow.
            Ansel Packer is scheduled to die in twelve hours. He knows what he\'s done, and now awaits execution, the same chilling fate he forced on those girls, years ago. But Ansel doesn\'t want to die; he wants to be celebrated, understood. He hoped it wouldn\'t end like this, not for him.
            Through a kaleidoscope of women—a mother, a sister, a homicide detective—we learn the story of Ansel\'s life. We meet his mother, Lavender, a seventeen-year-old girl pushed to desperation; Hazel, twin sister to Ansel\'s wife, inseparable since birth, forced to watch helplessly as her sister\'s relationship threatens to devour them all; and finally, Saffy, the homicide detective hot on his trail, who has devoted herself to bringing bad men to justice but struggles to see her own life clearly. As the clock ticks down, these three women sift through the choices that culminate in tragedy, exploring the rippling fissures that such destruction inevitably leaves in its wake.
            Blending breathtaking suspense with astonishing empathy, Notes on an Execution presents a chilling portrait of womanhood as it simultaneously unravels the familiar narrative of the American serial killer, interrogating our system of justice and our cultural obsession with crime stories, asking readers to consider the false promise of looking for meaning in the psyches of violent men.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelmaid">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Mystery · Fiction · Mystery Thriller · Audiobook · Thriller · Contemporary · Crime · Adult · Adult Fiction · Suspense</item>
        <item>Molly Gray is not like everyone else. She struggles with social skills and misreads the intentions of others. Her gran used to
            interpret the world for her, codifying it into simple rules that Molly could live by.
            Since Gran died a few months ago, twenty-five-year-old Molly has been navigating life\'s complexities all by herself.
            No matter—she throws herself with gusto into her work as a hotel maid. Her unique character, along with her obsessive love
            of cleaning and proper etiquette, make her an ideal fit for the job. She delights in donning her crisp uniform each morning,
            stocking her cart with miniature soaps and bottles, and returning guest rooms at the Regency Grand Hotel to a state of
            perfection.
            But Molly\'s orderly life is upended the day she enters the suite of the infamous and wealthy Charles Black, only to find
            it in a state of disarray and Mr. Black himself dead in his bed. Before she knows what\'s happening, Molly\'s unusual demeanor
            has the police targeting her as their lead suspect. She quickly finds herself caught in a web of deception, one she has no
            idea how to untangle. Fortunately for Molly, friends she never knew she had unite with her in a search for clues to what
            really happened to Mr. Black—but will they be able to find the real killer before it\'s too late?
            A Clue-like, locked-room mystery and a heartwarming journey of the spirit, The Maid explores what it means to be the same
            as everyone else and yet entirely different—and reveals that all mysteries can be solved through connection to the human heart.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelparisapartment">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Mystery · Thriller · Fiction · Suspense · Adult · Contemporary · Adult Fiction</item>
        <item>From the New York Times bestselling author of The Guest List comes a new locked room mystery, set in a Paris apartment building in which every resident has something to hide…
            Jess needs a fresh start. She\'s broke and alone, and she\'s just left her job under less than ideal circumstances. Her half-brother Ben didn\'t sound thrilled when she asked if she could crash with him for a bit, but he didn\'t say no, and surely everything will look better from Paris. Only when she shows up – to find a very nice apartment, could Ben really have afforded this? – he\'s not there.
            The longer Ben stays missing, the more Jess starts to dig into her brother\'s situation, and the more questions she has. Ben\'s neighbors are an eclectic bunch, and not particularly friendly. Jess may have come to Paris to escape her past, but it\'s starting to look like it\'s Ben\'s future that\'s in question.
            The socialite – The nice guy – The alcoholic – The girl on the verge – The concierge
            Everyone\'s a neighbor. Everyone\'s a suspect. And everyone knows something they\'re not telling.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelaflickerinthedark">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Thriller · Mystery · Fiction · Suspense · Adult · Contemporary</item>
        <item>When Chloe Davis was twelve, six teenage girls went missing in her small Louisiana town. By the end of the summer, Chloe\'s father had been arrested as a serial killer and promptly put in prison. Chloe and the rest of her family were left to grapple with the truth and try to move forward while dealing with the aftermath.
            Now 20 years later, Chloe is a psychologist in private practice in Baton Rouge and getting ready for her wedding. She finally has a fragile grasp on the happiness she\'s worked so hard to get. Sometimes, though, she feels as out of control of her own life as the troubled teens who are her patients. And then a local teenage girl goes missing,
            and then another, and that terrifying summer comes crashing back. Is she paranoid, and seeing parallels that aren\'t really there, or for the second time in her life, is she about to unmask a killer?
            In a debut novel that has already been optioned for a limited series by actress Emma Stone and sold to a dozen countries around the world, Stacy Willingham has created an unforgettable character in a spellbinding thriller that will appeal equally to fans of Gillian Flynn and Karin Slaughter.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelbookofcoldcases">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Mystery · Thriller · Fiction · Horror · Fantasy · Adult · Suspense</item>
        <item>In 1977, Claire Lake, Oregon, was shaken by the Lady Killer Murders: Two men, seemingly randomly, were murdered with the same gun,
            with strange notes left behind. Beth Greer was the perfect suspect—a rich, eccentric twenty-three-year-old woman, seen
            fleeing one of the crimes. But she was acquitted, and she retreated to the isolation of her mansion.
            Oregon, 2017. Shea Collins is a receptionist, but by night, she runs a true crime website, the Book of Cold Cases—a passion
            fueled by the attempted abduction she escaped as a child. When she meets Beth by chance, Shea asks her for an interview.
            To Shea\'s surprise, Beth says yes.
            They meet regularly at Beth\'s mansion, though Shea is never comfortable there. Items move when she\'s not looking, and she
            could swear she\'s seen a girl outside the window. The allure of learning the truth about the case from the smart, charming Beth
            is too much to resist, but even as they grow closer, Shea senses something isn\'t right. Is she making friends with a manipulative
            murderer, or are there other dangers lurking in the darkness of the Greer house?
            A true crime blogger gets more than she bargained for while interviewing the woman acquitted of two cold case slayings in this
            chilling new novel from the New York Times bestselling author of The Sun Down Motel.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelitgirl">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Mystery · Thriller · Fiction · Mystery Thriller · Audiobook · Suspense · Adult · Crime · Contemporary · Adult Fiction</item>
        <item>April Coutts-Cliveden was the first person Hannah Jones met at Oxford.
            Vivacious, bright, occasionally vicious, and the ultimate It girl, she quickly pulled Hannah into her dazzling orbit. Together, they developed a group of devoted and inseparable friends—Will, Hugh, Ryan, and Emily—during their first term. By the end of the second, April was dead.
            Now, a decade later, Hannah and Will are expecting their first child, and the man convicted of killing April, former Oxford porter John Neville, has died in prison. Relieved to have finally put the past behind her, Hannah\'s world is rocked when a young journalist comes knocking and presents new evidence that Neville may have been innocent. As Hannah reconnects with old friends and delves deeper into the mystery of April\'s death, she realizes that the friends she thought she knew all have something to hide... including a murder.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="novelallgoodpeople">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Mystery · Thriller · Fiction · Suspense · Adult · Contemporary · Adult Fiction</item>
        <item>In the propulsive debut novel from the host of the 1st true crime podcast "Crime Junkie," a journalist uncovers her hometown\'s dark secrets when she becomes obsessed with the unsolved murder of her childhood neighbor—and the disappearance of another girl twenty years later.
            Everyone from Wakarusa, Indiana, remembers the case of January Jacobs, who was found dead in a ditch hours after her family awoke to find her gone. Margot Davies was six at the time, the same age as January—and they were next-door neighbors. In the twenty years since, Margot has grown up, moved away, and become a big-city journalist, but she\'s always been haunted by the fear that it could\'ve been her. And the worst part is, January\'s killer has never been brought to justice.
            When Margot returns home to help care for her sick uncle, it feels like walking into a time capsule. Wakarusa is exactly how she remembered: genial, stifled, secretive. Then news breaks about five-year-old Natalie Clark from the next town over, who\'s gone missing under eerily similar circumstances. With all the old feelings rushing back, Margot vows to find Natalie and solve January\'s murder once and for all.
            But the police, the family, the townspeople—they all seem to be hiding something. And the deeper Margot digs into Natalie\'s disappearance, the more resistance she encounters, and the colder January\'s case feels. Could the killer still be out there? Could it be the same person who kidnapped Natalie? And what will it cost to finally discover what truly happened that night?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="noveldaisydarker">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Mystery · Thriller · Mystery Thriller · Fiction · Audiobook · Suspense · Adult · Horror · Crime · Contemporary</item>
        <item>The New York Times bestselling Queen of Twists returns...with a family reunion that leads to murder.
            After years of avoiding each other, Daisy Darker\'s entire family is assembling for Nana\'s 80th birthday party in Nana\'s crumbling gothic house on a tiny tidal island. Finally back together one last time, when the tide comes in, they will be cut off from the rest of the world for eight hours.
            The family arrives, each of them harboring secrets. Then at the stroke of midnight, as a storm rages, Nana is found dead. And an hour later, the next family member follows...
            Trapped on an island where someone is killing them one by one, the Darkers must reckon with their present mystery as well as their past secrets, before the tide comes in and all is revealed.
            With a wicked wink to Agatha Christie\'s And Then There Were None, Daisy Darker\'s unforgettable twists will leave readers reeling.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="noveljackal">
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>Horror · Mystery · Thriller · Fiction · Mystery Thriller · Adult · Suspense · Audiobook · Contemporary · Fantasy</item>
        <item>A young Black girl goes missing in the woods outside her white Rust Belt town. But she\'s not the first—and she may not be the last. . . .
            It\'s watching.
            Liz Rocher is coming home . . . reluctantly. As a Black woman, Liz doesn\'t exactly have fond memories of Johnstown, Pennsylvania, a predominantly white town. But her best friend is getting married, so she braces herself for a weekend of awkward and passive-aggressive reunions. Liz has grown, though; she can handle whatever awaits her. But on the day of the wedding, somewhere between dancing and dessert, the bride\'s daughter, Caroline, goes missing—and the only thing left behind is a piece of white fabric covered in blood.
            It\'s taking.
            As a frantic search begins, with the police combing the trees for Caroline, Liz is the only one who notices a pattern: a summer night. A missing girl. A party in the woods. She\'s seen this before. Keisha Woodson, the only other Black girl in school, walked into the woods with a mysterious man and was later found with her chest cavity ripped open and her heart missing. Liz shudders at the thought that it could have been her, and now, with Caroline missing, it can\'t be a coincidence. As Liz starts to dig through the town\'s history, she uncovers a horrifying secret about the place she once called home. Children have been going missing in these woods for years. All of them Black. All of them girls.
            It\'s your turn.
            With the evil in the forest creeping closer, Liz knows what she must do: find Caroline, or be entirely consumed by the darkness.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>